<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Art With Yael</string>
    <string name="profile_description">
        This is a piece of text which I suppose, at some point in the next three years, will be replaced by a (common adjective alert) beautiful description of why Yael loves painting and what it means to her to create these stunning works of art. I\'ve just checked this message and it\'s not long enough for my testing so here\'s some extra words to take up more space. Even this isn\'t enough now that I\'ve added my Scroll View thingy so this extra sentence is essentially so that I will be able to determine if the Scroll View is fully functional. By that, I mean I want to check if I am able to scroll through the page. I now need to try another scroll view which is higher up the page so I\'ll have to repeat this whole piece of writing. This is a piece of text which I suppose, at some point in the next three years, will be replaced by a (common adjective alert) beautiful description of why Yael loves painting and what it means to her to create these stunning works of art. I\'ve just checked this message and it\'s not long enough for my testing so here\'s some extra words to take up more space. Even this isn\'t enough now that I\'ve added my Scroll View thingy so this extra sentence is essentially so that I will be able to determine if the Scroll View is fully functional. By that, I mean I want to check if I am able to scroll through the page. This still isn\'t long enough so I\'ll try again. This is a piece of text which I suppose, at some point in the next three years, will be replaced by a (common adjective alert) beautiful description of why Yael loves painting and what it means to her to create these stunning works of art. I\'ve just checked this message and it\'s not long enough for my testing so here\'s some extra words to take up more space. Even this isn\'t enough now that I\'ve added my Scroll View thingy so this extra sentence is essentially so that I will be able to determine if the Scroll View is fully functional. By that, I mean I want to check if I am able to scroll through the page.
    </string>

</resources>
